▍2026 美网 男单半决赛
兹维列夫 6-3 7-6⁷ 7-6⁶ 哈恰诺夫 · 赛后场上采访
You've been at the very very top
你稳居这项运动的最顶端
of the game now
已经有一段时间了
for a while, but this year you've made
但今年你打进了
back-to-back-to-back finals of majors,
连续三个大满贯决赛
including the win in Roland Garros.
其中还拿下了法网冠军
Has something changed
有什么东西变了吗
this year compared to maybe the last four
今年 和过去四五年
or five years for you?
比起来
Yeah. at the end of last year,
是啊 去年年底
I did your podcast
我上了你的播客
which is called Nothing Major
那节目叫 Nothing Major
and then I decided to have some majors
然后我决定去拿几个大满贯
in me because I didn't want
因为我不想
to do that podcast again.
再上一次那个播客
No, but look,
不过说实话
sometimes just things go your way
有时候事情就是会站在你这边
and I feel like I've had a lot of struggle
我觉得我在大满贯这一关
at at the major level.
挣扎了很久
I was so close so many times
太多次都只差一点点
and maybe maybe this year God
也许今年是上天
has has said that, you know, this is going
告诉我 这一年
to be your year and just enjoy the time
是属于你的 好好享受
on your on the court.
在球场上的每一刻
And, I'm enjoying it.
我确实在享受
I love playing these these big finals
我喜欢打这种大决赛
and I can't wait for Sunday.
我已经等不及周日了
And finally, on Sunday, you're going
最后一个问题 周日
to play an American out on this court.
你要在这里对上一个美国人
The atmosphere is going to be incredible.
气氛一定会非常疯狂
I'm not sure how much
我不太确定
crowd support you're going
你能得到多少
to have, but are you looking forward
现场的支持 但你期待吗
to what's going to transpire
期待周日在这片场地上
on this court Sunday playing an American
对上一个美国人
for the final?
打这场决赛
Yeah, I think I think it's going
是啊 我觉得那会
to be incredible, incredibly special.
非常特别 特别特别
Especially these two guys, Frances
尤其是这两个人 蒂亚福
and Ben, they're the crowd favorites here
和谢尔顿 他们在纽约
in New York.
是所有人的宠儿
Everybody loves them and I think to tonight
所有人都爱他们 我觉得今晚
is going to be an absolutely epic semi-final
会是一场史诗级的半决赛
and I'm looking forward to to watching it
我很期待看这场球
and yeah, hopefully I can I cannot make
希望我能 我不会
the American dream come true on Sunday.
让美国梦在周日成真
Are you going to watch that match tonight?
你今晚会看那场球吗
Yeah, of course everybody will.
当然 所有人都会看
All right, into the final.
好的 晋级决赛